ANGEL HOSHI 2.0
Model edit and OC belong to AnnietheCloud
- Do not edit or redistribute this model. If you find mistakes then please tell me and i will try to fix. If you want to know where i found a part i will tell you
- No use over PG17 without permission
- No claiming as your own.
- No OutOfCharacter use. ( See Profile below for information )
- Credit if used.
- Link me if possible when used

You know, the usual rules for edited models that are OCs. Yeah c:

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

there are alot of parts on these models so i'm not gonna list them.

Models included in pack:
• Angel [Base]
• Angel [2 Casuals]
• Angel [Pj]
• Senka [Base]
• Senka [2 Casuals]
• Human Angel

ALL ARE EDIT LOCKED

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Profile:


- Name: Angel Louise Hoshi
- Nickname: Angie, Lou Lou.
- Age: 17 years old, Stuck in 15.
- Nationality: Born in Britain. British mother, french father.
- Birthday: 4th April
- Species: Vampire
- Sexual Tendencies: Straight
- Love interest: Edaurdo la Croix ( :devlunassis: ) - BOYFRIEND
- Best friends:
• Niko
• Celeste
• Vivian

- Height: -
- Weight: -
- Favorite food: She is a vampire so she feeds on blood. Even so since she is a young vampire she is not used to this diet so - she eats normal food as well.
- Likes: Cooking, Baking, Games, Playing Guitar.
- Dislikes: The smell of blood -Only if its very strong and Human- ( It makes her 'twin'/split personality come out -I'll explain later- )

- Personality: Angel is very happy go lucky and somwhat carefree. when angel was turned into a vampire senka awakened inside her. angel does not the blood so often starves herself off it even though as a fairly new vampire she needs it to survive. so when she gets hungry/thirsty senka takes over. senka is the more evil side of angel. while angel is innocent and happy, senka is the complete opposite and will not stop until she gets what she wants (whether its blood, sex, etcetc). the inbetween stage is a stage where angel is yandere but not in the I WILL KILL EVERYONE WHO GETS NEAR MY BELOVED kinda way. an example of this is when her parents and younger sister aimi died. she became very depressed and hurt herself as she was afraid of hurting others. but she does get crazy and kinda murderous too.

- Related Characters:
• Candy (Younger Sister)
• Akuma (Older Brother)

- Extra Info: 
• Is a very skilled baker. She hopes to open her own bakery one day.
• She can play Piano, Guitar and Violin.
• She has infact three siblings in total. Two are Alive (Akuma and Candy), and one died of a disease while she was very young. (She always travels to her birthplace to visit her grave on the day she died - valentines day)
• She cannot yet fully control her vampire powers (speed, strength etc). She is learning to use them with Edaurdo and his sister Celeste.
• She is somewhat physcic (a power she gained when she became a vampire). She cannot control this yet. For example, when her thoughts are unstable (shes embarressed or ill/weak) her thoughts and memories are unwillingly transfered to those closest to her. 
• She has glasses but doesn't wear them. Instead she uses contacts but these hurt her eyes.


- Bio: 

When Angel was younger her younger sister Aimi got a disease that rotted her from the inside out. She died at age 2 on her birthday (Valentines day). A year later Candy was born and angel promised her there and then that she would protect candy. A week after candy was born their parents died in a car accident. Akuma got a job in a gay bar to fund them and angel stayed at home looking after candy learning how to cook and clean. But the tragic lost of three of her family members took its toll on angel and she started to cut. She got bullied in school for this and one day got attacked on the streets. She has a scar on her leg from the attack and she always tried to cover it up in shame. She eventually stopped cutting and at age 14 decided to get a private tutor for both her and candy so she could look after candy herself while learning. At age 16 she was attacked in the streets by a vampire after coming home from shopping. Someone saved her though who she later learned was Edaurdo. They fell in love and angel didn't know he was a vampire for a while. She asked if he could turn her into one for she didn't want to be apart from edaurdo if she died in the future. Although she knew the risks of this he agreed to. They lived together for a while but never saw much of eachother. Edaurdo came home one day and told angel that he would be travelling for a while and that they should split up. They still loved eachother and a few weeks later edaurdo came back. He found angel crying and asked if she would like to travel the world with him. Even though the journey is dangerous she agreed and they are now on a journey looking for a vampire. Although that is all Edaurdo will say not wanting to alarm angel.