KATIE ARCHIBALD 1.2

Model edit and OC belong to AnnietheCloud
- Do not edit or redistribute this model. If you find mistakes then please tell me and i will try to fix. If you want to know where i found a part i will tell you
- No use over PG17 without permission
- No claiming as your own.
- No OutOfCharacter use. ( See Profile below for information )
- Credit if used.
- Link me if possible when used

You know, the usual rules for edited models that are OCs. Yeah c:

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

there are alot of parts on these models so i'm not gonna list them.

Models included in pack:
• Base
• 2 Casuals
• Pj
• Swimsuit

ALL ARE EDIT LOCKED

---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Profile:


- Name: Katie Archibald
- Nickname: None
- Age: 15
- Nationality: Italian.
- Birthday: 5th January
- Species: Cat Demon
- Sexual Tendencies: Straight
- Love interest(s): - Daniel ( :devizzy-chan2095: ) - BOYFRIEND
- Best friends:
• Story
• Daniel
• Nathan
- Height: -
- Weight: -
- Favorite food: Tuna and Sushi
- Likes: Photography, Jogging, Meat, Purple, Fish, Stuffed Toys.
- Dislikes: Rain, Water, Lightning, Being called cute or a princess.

- Personality: Katie is a bit of a tsundere. But she means well. She's really kind otherwise and enjoys a good laugh with her friends. She is not good at making friends mostly because of her trust issues. The only person she trusts is Brianna and she tries to push other people away from Brianna thinking its the best for her.

- Related Characters:
• Brianna - OLDER SISTER

- Extra Info: 
• She is really overprotective her her older sister. When Brianna goes on dates or is around any boys, Katie and Story tend to spy on her to make sure she doesn't get hurt.
• She loves photography
• She also loves jogging and goes for jogs in the morning daily.
• She is deathly afraid of rain and thunder storms. She often cries and screams through them.


- Bio: 

Katie was born into a rich family. Her dad being the duke of savoy. He didn't like Katie very much and very often abused her. She ran away from home when she was 13 to find her older sister Brianna who ran away. She has trust issues and finds it hard to trust anyone. She does get angry quickly and looses her temper when she is annoyed.